(Sheldon:)...and then returned it to me,
hoping I wouldn't notice.
(Sheldon:)Would you characterize that
as responsible?
(Page:)That's really not the sort of
thing we're interested in.
(Sheldon:)You heard me say
Blu-ray, right?
(Leonard:)I did.
(Sheldon:)Very well.
(Sheldon:)Would you be interested
(Sheldon:)in knowing that Mr. Wolowitz
once snuck onto
(Sheldon:)my World of Warcraft account
and changed the name
(Sheldon:)of a certain level-80 warlock
from Sheldor to Smeldor?
(Page:)I'm afraid not.
(Page:)Is there anything else?
"Is there anything else?"
(Sheldon:)Where would you like to start?
(Sheldon:)He refuses to pay fines
(Sheldon:)when he's overdue
with books I lend him.
(Sheldon:)He crashed the Mars Rover while
attempting to impress a woman.
(Sheldon:)He recommended that I go see
the third Matrix movie
because it was, and I quote,
"just as good
as the first one."
(Sheldon:)If that's not irresponsible,
I don't know what is.
(Page:)The Mars Rover?